[{"answer": "I don't think they know the answer to that question.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Who do they think you think instinctively go beat Obama?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "I mean, do you think that somebody like Michele Bachmann or Sarah Palin could ever actually win an election?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "At the moment, in the next few years in this country?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "It's always going to be the problem.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Or does the rather intransigent streak that they bring to all that policy-making, is that always going to be the problem?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, I think the answer is both.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Has he been disappointing or simply was it that expectation levels were way too high?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "I think he has it in him.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Has he got it in him, do you think?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Yes, a little Elmer Gantry thrown in.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "I mean, bordering on Joel Olsteen stuff, Frank?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "I mean, is he somebody who could have his day?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "I think he has to be.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "I'm getting a sense that although he said to me absolutely no way am I going to run in 2012, he is coming under pressure, do you think from Republicans to chuck his hat in the ring?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "ICH: Well, a few good things can be said.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "What's your assessment of where the spoils of victory and defeat have worked themselves out?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Not really.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Do you subscribe to any of that theory?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I'm going to be quietly in New York.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "How do you intend to commemorate it?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I didn't realize you could give away a person on that show.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "Why are you one of Oprah's favorite things?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Look, as me, if it were me, and it is, I have always scratched my head about that.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "What was so special about you?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I wish that I could use my own music in the same kind of way.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Have you ever used Josh Groban music?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Oh, there is always a muse.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 404, "question": "Would there be someone you were thinking of?", "qSentId": 403}, {"answer": "The bad-ass.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "What is the bad-ass?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Never done any drugs.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "You ever been a hopeless drunk, a drug addict?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "I'm a control freak.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "Are you a fighter?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "I do love it.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Do you like it?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I've been asked in the past and I've politely turned it down, just because you can't top that.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Can you do it with anyone's?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "No, I haven't because I'm weird.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "You've never slept with a groupie?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "ORGAN: They won't complain, because it's obviously like a badge of honor.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Who was it?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Have you interviewed Kid Rock?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "Not at the moment, no.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "You want to share with me?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 571, "question": "Do you ever sing to your ladies?", "qSentId": 570}, {"answer": "It's now called the Find Your Light Foundation, which is to me how I felt --", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "What is it now?", "qSentId": 593}, {"answer": "If they want to, they can visit my website, which is FindYourLightFoundation.org.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 596, "question": "How can people help if they want to?", "qSentId": 595}, {"answer": "You raise me up.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "Can you give me one last burst of \"Raise Me Up\"?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "I didn't even ask the question.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Are you trying to say I need to have a baby?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Only God knows.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "Can we expect the little patter of little Beyonce and Jay-Zs?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "I will.", "docId": "110901pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "Would you mind asking him to tell me?", "qSentId": 659}]